http://www.sennheiser.com/privacy

AMBEO VR Mic
AMBEO Smart Headset (archived)
Sennheiser Control Cockpit
Digitize your AV management workflow.
Digital workflows for flawless daily business.
For free and easy to use.
Read more...
Privacy
Information on data protection and data security at Sennheiser electronic GmbH & Co. KG
as of May 25, 2018
1.Introduction
This policy applies to any websites operated by Sennheiser electronic GmbH & Co. KG (hereinafter referred to as “Sennheiser”). Other policies may apply to other third-party servers and websites.
When you visit our website, your personal data will be collected by us.
As we take the protection of personal data very seriously, we like to inform you which personal data exactly is stored and how this data is used.
We are subject to the provisions of the European General Data Protection Regulation (DSGVO), the Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) and the Telemedia Act (TMG) and have taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure that these data protection regulations are observed.
2.Controller
Sennheiser electronic GmbH & Co. KG
Am Labor 1
30900 Wedemark
Germany
Tel .: +49 (0) 5130 600 0
Fax: +49 (0) 5130 600 1300
E-Mail: [email protected]
Further details can be found in the imprint.
3.Data Protection Officer
For questions about this privacy policy, you can also contact the Sennheiser Data Protection Officer:
PwC Cyber Security Services GmbH
Kapelle-Ufer 4, 10117 BerlinGermany
e-mail: [email protected]
4.Handling of personal data
Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; a natural person is regarded as identifiable, which can be identified directly or indirectly, in particular by association with an identifier such as a name, with an identification number, with location data, with an online identifier or with one or more special features.
5.Collected data, purposes of data processing and legal basis
Every time a user accesses a Sennheiser page and every time a file is accessed, data about that process is stored in a log file. Depending on the access protocol used, the log record contains information with the following contents:
IP address of the requesting computer
Name of the requested file
Date and time of the request
Desired access methods / functions from the requesting computer
Access status of the web server
The URL from which the file was requested
Operating system and browser type or browser settings.
No usage profiles are created that link IP addresses and personally identifiable information. Something different is only valid if this is defined separately in this policy.
The stored data will be used exclusively for purposes of technical content provision, identification and tracking of inadmissible access attempts / accesses to the web server as well as for statistical evaluations such as visitor numbers and page popularity. The evaluation is carried out only by authorized employees of Sennheiser.
6.Use of cookies
As part of your visit to our website, we use cookies if you consented to it or this is technically required for providing our services to you. These are small text files that are stored on your computer through our web application and through which we can recognize your internet browser. The common internet browsers are set to automatically accept cookies. However, you can disable it or set your Internet browser to notify you of the use of cookies.
The cookie data is not used to personally identify you.
Persistent cookies are stored on your computer for 7 days and are designed to give you the most comfortable use of our website beyond the current visit and are used by us for the purpose of displaying individual content.
If you do not want to allow persistent cookies, you can do so by disabling them in your browser. For details on the procedure, please refer to the help function in the menu bar of your browser. The deactivation of persistent cookies does not affect the usability of our site in general.
Session cookies are only stored on your system until your current browser session is closed. They serve to give you an unlimited use of our services for the current visit of our site. These data are anonymous, so you are not personally identifiable.
If you do not want to allow session cookies, you can do so by disabling session cookies in your browser. For details on the procedure, please refer to the help function in the menu bar of your browser.
By deactivating session cookies, we cannot guarantee that you will be able to use all our services without restriction.
7.Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. However, in the event of activation of IP anonymisation on this website, your IP address will be shortened beforehand by Google within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states of the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be sent to a Google server in the US and shortened there. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide other services related to website activity and internet usage to the website operator. The IP address provided by Google Analytics as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with other Google data. You can prevent the storage of cookies by a corresponding setting of your browser software. In addition, you may prevent the collection by Google of the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) as well as the processing of this data by Google by using the link below http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en to download and install the available browser plugin.
For more information about Terms of Use and Privacy, please visit http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/en.html or https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/.
We point out that on this website Google Analytics has been extended by the code "anonymizeIp" to ensure an anonymous collection of IP addresses (so-called IP-Masking).
8.Google Double Click
Sennheiser's website uses Doubleblick by Google. Doubleclick by Google uses cookies to show you advertisements that are relevant to you. Your browser will be assigned a pseudonymous identification number (ID) to check which ads have appeared in your browser and which ads have been viewed. The cookies themselves contain no personal information, according to Google. Using the DoubleClick cookie allows Google and its affiliate websites to serve ads based on previous visits to our or other websites on the Internet. The information generated by the cookies is transmitted by Google for evaluation to a server in the USA and stored there. Google transmits the data to third parties only because of legal regulations or order processing.
By using our web pages, you agree to the processing of the data collected about you by Google and the manner described above, the data processing and the stated purpose. You may prevent the collection by Google of the data generated by the cookies and related to your use of the Website and the processing of such data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available from DoubleClick's deactivation extension: https://www.google. com / settings / ads / plugin
9.Google GA Audiences / Remarinessing feature
The website uses Google's remarketing feature. The Remarketing feature allows Google to determine which pages visitors to the Google Network have viewed to display interest-based advertising to users. According to Google, no personal information is collected during this process.
Google's Remarketing feature can be disabled at http://www.google.com/settings/ads
10.Facebook Remarketing / Retargeting (Custom Audiences Pixel)
The website uses the "Custom Audiences" remarketing feature of Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook"). By means of this function and the use of the corresponding remarketing tag from Facebook, we may target users with advertising by displaying interest-based personalized Facebook ads when they visit Facebook.
When visiting the Sennheiser website, a direct link to the Facebook servers is made via the Facebook remarketing tags. The Facebook server communicates which of the Sennheiser websites you have visited. Facebook assigns this information to your personal Facebook user account.
For more information about the processing of data by Facebook and your rights and privacy opportunities, please refer to the Facebook Privacy Policy at https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/. If you do not want Facebook to associate the collected information directly with your Facebook user account, you can disable the "Custom Audiences" remarketing feature in your Facebook profile, which requires you to log in there.
11.Contact form/ comment functions
Personal data, provided by using a contact form or a comment function on the website will be transferred to Sennheiser. When you use the comment function your comment will be published on the website including your name.
Personal data provided by you will be transferred to us via secured connection and SSL (Secure-Socket-Layer) encrypted. We are using 256 bit encryption. The SSL encryption (identified by https:// in the address of the website of the internet browser) is a protocol for the encryption of data during the transfer from the webserver to the internet browser. During the transfer between the user’s computer and the SSl server the personal data are SSL encrypted.
12.Automated decision-making; profiling
Automated decision-making / profiling does not take place.
13.Supervisory Authority
You have the right to receive free information about your data stored by Sennheiser.
In addition, you have the right to ask for
correction of incorrect data
restriction of processing
deletion of data
objection to the data processing and
data portability.
There is a right of appeal to the supervisory authority responsible for Sennheiser. The contact details are:
The State Commissioner for Data Protection Niedersachsen
Prinzenstraße 5
30159 Hanover, Germany
Telephone + 49 (0) 511 120 4500
Fax + 49 (0) 511 120 4599
E-Mail: [email protected]
14.Amendments
Since Sennheiser's website may be subject to change, it may be necessary in individual cases to make changes to this policy. Sennheiser reserves the right to change this policy at any time. The most recent version of this policy can be found on http://www.sennheiser.com
